Devashish Trehan

Experienced Frontend Developer Creating User-Focused Web Experiences

Agra, Uttar Pradesh devtrehan.dt@gmail.com +91 95487 27092

Dedicated Front-end web developer with 4+ years experience of developing beautiful UI and extremely useful UX. Strong creative, analytical and problem solving skills. Team player with an eye for detail. knowledge of many JS libraries, Reactjs, Nextjs and vanilla javascript, typescript.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Work Experience

Sr. Associate Consultant - Frontend

Oodles Technologies-Gurugram, Haryana August 2022 to Present

Worked here as a front-end and Strapi developer.

I played an important role in creating captivating user interfaces and ensuring exceptional user experiences. My primary focus was on developing optimized and efficient applications, utilizing Next.js, Strapi CMS, Vue.js, and Nuxt.js.

Associate Consultant

Oodles Technologies-Gurgaon, Haryana June 2021 to July 2022

I have worked as a front-end developer and responsible for developing beautiful user interfaces and best user experience. Develops Application in manner so that those can be accessible.

Here I worked with Web3, metamask wallet, ethereum smart contract integrations and all.

Web Developer

Balj Services Private Limited-Noida, Uttar Pradesh October 2020 to May 2021

I work here as a front end web developer, who is responsible for making user interfaces of web applications using HTML, CSS, React.js, Next.js etc.

Web Developer

Technosters technologies-Agra, Uttar Pradesh June 2019 to September 2020

I have worked as a front-end developer and responsible for making User Interfaces of web applications, and have also worked as mobile application developer.

Here I have learned and used React Native to build android applications.

Education

Bachelor's in Computer science

Dr. Bhimrao Ambedkar University - Agra, Uttar Pradesh August 2017 to Present

Skills / IT Skills

- Html5 (3 years)
- Css (3 years)
- Javascript (3 years)
- Nodejs
- Reactjs (3 years)
- React native (Less than 1 year)
- Nextjs (2 years)
- react-redux (2 years)
- problem solving (3 years)
- Typescript (2 years)
- UI frameworks (2 years)
- Web3 (1 year)
- Decentralized Application (1 year)
- Git (3 years)

Languages

- Hindi Expert
- English Intermediate

Certifications and Licenses

CCC

July 2016 to Present

Projects / Papers Presented

Grocery store app

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.bringfresh

June 2020

It is an online grocery store which deliver products at home on order,

I have worked as a react native developer, and developed android app which facilitates users to easily order products

Staff and activity management

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.livetracker

August 2020

It is a staff and activity management system, which manages staff's daily attendance, trach their location, distance covered and keeps track of day-to-day activities like keeping track of orders, payments, meetings, etc.

I have worked as a react native developer, and developed android app.

Image manipulation application

September 2019

This is my college project,

It is a image manipulation application, which provides basic manipulations, like cropping, resizing, tunning, adding filters and text and making collages.

It also provides a personalized space for storing images on cloud, categorize them upload and download them.

Online Mock Examination Portal

http://admin.ourexamination.com

December 2019

It is an online examination portal for practice competitive and institutional exams, any institute can join this design test papers for their students.

I have worked as a front-end developer and made this project in Angular 8.

New Jobs Hub

http://www.newjobshub.com

December 2020

It is a job portal which provide information about jobs and companies,

I have worked as a front-end developer to develop the interface of the app using react.js.

College Disha

https://www.collegedisha.com

April 2021

It is a portal which provide information about colleges, universities for higher education and other education related stuff like news, articles etc.

As a part of its development team, I have developed its user interface in React.js, Next.js and other required technologies, to ensure server side rendering and better performance.

Sosh NFT

https://www.soshnft.io

2022

It is a decentralized application to create NFTs of social media posts, integrates with social media like, Instagram, twitter, youtube, tiktok.

It uses ethereum smart contracts to create NFT over ethereum blockchain.

Moments Auction

https://gamavrs.com/moments-auction

2021

It is an application to auction 3 dimensional NFT collections, These NFT are created on ethereum blockchain and users can place with for these collections.

Gamaverse

https://gamavrs.com/

2022

It is an application to provide random NFT avatars to users, which they can get by minting them. These avatars can be used in Games.

Gamaverse Admin panel

The admin dashboard to manage the moments-auction and gamaverse, The dashboard is the app to manage whole application, avatars, auto avatar generation, collections, and many more.

Casino Lobby

https://casino-lobby-bju.pages.dev/

2022

It is a web application made with vuejs . the App lists casino games from different suppliers and user can play the games. It is integrated in a desktop application to extend the functionalities of an app. here We used post-message for cross origin communication.

In App promotions

https://inapp-promo.pages.dev/

2023

It is vuejs app which lists the promotion listing and the detailed view. This application is an extension to a desktop application which is integrated with webview.

Casino Builder

January 2024

This project involves developing a drag-and-drop application designed for creating casino lobbies tailored to various regions.